Here are five tips to help you do things quickly.
One: Anywhere you are, open the guide by double-tapping the Xbox button on your controller.
Even while you’re playing you can send party invites and messages.
Two: From Home, jump straight down to your games and apps collection and pins
by pressing the right trigger.
Jump back up with the left trigger.
Three: If you’re playing a backward compatible Xbox 360 game,
open the 360 guide by pressing the Menu button and View button at the same time.
Four: Quickly capture a screenshot of your game,
or the last thirty seconds of game play,
by double-tapping the Xbox button and then pressing Y or X.
Five: If you have an app snapped, switch between it and your game
by double-tapping the Xbox button.
The guide opens with Unsnap highlighted.
Move right once and press A to switch to your game,
or twice and press “A” to switch to your snapped app.
Discover more! Get information and tips from Xbox Help.